(Howard:)-I just wanted to tell you I'm a big fan.
-Oh, thanks.
(Howard:)I'm sure you're probably sick
of Star Trek questions...
(Howard:)...but Whoopi Goldberg,
you ever hit that?
(Raj:)Ah. Beer.
(Raj:)The magic elixir that can turn this poor,
shy Indian boy into the life of the party.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah.
-Chili-cheese fry?
-Yes. I love chili-cheese fries.
(Leonard:)-Really? You love them?
-Yeah, why?
No reason. Just glad to hear...
(Leonard:)...you're comfortable
saying you love something.
-You wanna get into this right now?
-Get into what?
(Leonard:)Why wouldn't you love
the chili-cheese fries?
(Leonard:)They've been in your life a long time.
(Leonard:)They make you happy.
They deserve to know.
Okay, look, you caught me by surprise
last night. I didn't know what to say.
Now you've had time to think about it.
What do you wanna say?